# Sapotnitskiy Dmytro



Date of Birth: March 24, 1989

Phone number: +38 (097) 299 21 09

E-mail: dmytro.sapotnitskiy@gmail.com

Skype: shelby\_dima

Location: Kyiv

## Summary

I am learning Python and its frameworks (Django and Flask) by myself during 4 months. In the web development process, I also create functional (using Selenium) and unit tests. As a development environment, I use the platform cloud9 (https://c9.io). I use GITHUB to control versions of webprojects. I have read The Test-Driven Development with Python and The Definitive Guide to Django book. I passed courses on HTML & CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Python at codecademy.com. My knowledge of English is at intermediate level.

### **Work Experience**

«Tetra Pak Ukraine» – Packaging Materials Factory. P2 Administrator

05.2012 - today (2 months)

Making technical documentation which include problems and its solutions, iDoc handling between production system, SAP ERP R/3, SAP BO; support and teach users to work in SAP system. Additionally I supports local developed programs which are used in production process.

«ArcelorMittal Kryvyi Rih» – Metallurgical Plant. Consultant of SAP, PP module

02.2012 - 05.2016 (4 years and 3 months)

Making technical documentation, setting tasks for the development department; perform testing in a lab environment; support and teach users to work in SAP system in production accounting field.

«ML Company» (city Kryvyi Rih) – IT Integrator. System and Network Designer

06.2011-01.2012 (4 months)

Make design of communication networks, development of technical documentation for the project, installation of active and passive equipment according to the project

# Key achievements

- Heat report for Steel Making Shop and Heat report for CCM heats. They include data gathering from shop flour system and display it to staff. Personnel make decisions and enter them based on displayed data. Also, they can print heat report. This data transfers to other shop flor systems.
- Take part in implementation team of Make-to-Order project in Repair Department. Make programs for mass load of basic data from legacy systems. Develop Excel macros using VBA which needed for automatization of data preparing process.
- Prepared RFQ[Request for Proposal] for MES which included main requirements and description of current situation at Plant.

• Take part in Hackathon. The theme was "Tools". Our team taken second place. Our project was called "Tool for monitoring road conditions". The core of our solution was Arduino Uno which collect data form weight and temperature sensors and send it to the server.

### Education

I graduated Kryvyi Rih Technical University in 2011 with "Specialist in computer systems and networks" Diploma.

## Additional information

#### Languages:

- English intermediate level of knowledge;
- Ukrainian is native language;
- Russian is second native language.

#### Personal Skills:

- Learning Python programing language and Django framework
- Analytical thinking
- Responsible person
- Work in team